Faculty of Education fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Office of the Dean of Education files, 1965 - 1984; F-233-1; 62 cm of textual records 4 architectural drawings; General note: the architectural drawings are found in sub-series 2, file 35.
  - Dean of Education subject files, 1965 - 1984; F-233-1-2; 27 cm of textual records; General note: the architectural drawings are found in file 35.
    - Certification Advisory Committee, 1974; F-233-1-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 233-3)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-373.
    - Historical sketch, [1974?]; F-233-1-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 233-3)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-1-0-1.
    - Statistical analysis of student enrollment and graduates, 1975; F-233-1-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 233-3)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-3-0-2.
    - Correspondence, 1976; F-233-1-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 233-3)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-28.
    - Faculty symposium, 1976; F-233-1-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 233-3)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-3-0-3.
    - Staffing, 1976 - 1978; F-233-1-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 233-3)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-3-0-6.
    - Post-Graduation Activities of 1977-78 SFU Graduates, 1978; F-233-1-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 233-3)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-255.
    - Space allocation - MPX, 1978; F-233-1-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 233-51)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-3-0-5.
    - Report to the faculty: Dean Ivany, 1980; F-233-1-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 233-51)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-3-0-1.
    - R. Walker, D. Nadaner: Proposal for a Minor in Arts Education, 1981; F-233-1-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 233-51)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-101.
    - Learning Resources Centre, 1982; F-233-1-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 233-51)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-5-0-2.
    - Bachelor of Education proposal, 1983; F-233-1-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 233-51)
    - Faculty of Education submission to the President's Advisory Committee on University Priorities (PACUP), 1984; F-233-1-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 233-51)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-7-0-430.
    - Space allocation, vol. 2, 1968 - 1977; F-233-1-2-0-35
      Textual records; Architectural drawings
  - Administrative Assistant to the Dean correspondence, 1976 - 1982; F-233-1-3; 19 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records made or received by Stan Kanehara, Administrative Assistant to the Dean of Education, in the course of providing administrative support to the faculty over a seven-year period (1976-1982). Activities documented include management of physical facilities and infrastructure, budget planning and financial transactions, committee administrative support, and faculty-wide dissemination of information. Records include correspondence, master copies of wide-distribution memoranda, policies, proposals, invoices, schedules, leases, statistics, and forms. Note that correspondence for 1979 is missing.
    The material was originally stored in binders, filed chronologically.
    No further accruals are expected.
    - Correspondence, 1976 - 1980; F-233-1-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-15.
    - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1977; F-233-1-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-18.
    - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1977; F-233-1-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-19.
    - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1977; F-233-1-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-20.
    - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1977; F-233-1-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-21.
    - Correspondence, vol. 5, 1977; F-233-1-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-22.
    - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1978; F-233-1-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-23.
    - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1978; F-233-1-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-24.
    - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1978; F-233-1-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-25.
    - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1978; F-233-1-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-1-2-0-26.
    - Correspondence, 1980; F-233-1-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 233-70)
    - Correspondence, 1981; F-233-1-3-0-12 (Archival box - small 233-71)
    - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1982; F-233-1-3-0-13 (Archival box - small 233-71)
    - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1982; F-233-1-3-0-14 (Archival box - small 233-71)
- Joint Board of Teacher Education files, 1963 - 1982; F-233-2; 49 cm of textual records; Joint Board of Teacher Education
  The Joint Board of Teacher Education (JBTE) was established by the Province of British Columbia in 1963, in the revision of the University Act, whereby Simon Fraser University and the University of Victoria came into existence alongside the University of British Columbia. The JBTE comprised representatives from each of the universities, their Faculties of Education, the Ministry of Education, the Department of Education, the BC School Trustees Association, and the BC Teachers Federation. Its mandate was to ensure the high quality of teacher instruction in the province by reviewing the curriculum, staffing, budget, and facilities of the Faculties of Education; to make recommendations to the universities and the Ministry; and to initiate changes to teacher training. The JBTE was the successor to the Joint Board of College of Education (1955-1963). It was abolished in the 1983 amendment of the University Act.
  Series consists of records made or receive by the Dean of Education in the Dean's capacity as an officer of JBTE. Activities documented include Board meetings, program reviews and proposals, policy recommendations, and liaison with the provincial government and other educational agencies and institutes. Records include meeting agendas, minutes, reports, correspondence, proposals and course descriptions, recommendations, meeting schedules, budget statements, reprints and other reference material.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1963; F-233-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-1.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1964; F-233-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-2.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1965; F-233-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-3.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1966; F-233-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-4.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1967; F-233-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-5.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1968; F-233-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-6.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1969; F-233-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-7.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1970; F-233-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-8.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1970; F-233-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-9.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1971; F-233-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-10.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1972; F-233-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 233-28)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-11.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1972; F-233-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-12.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1972; F-233-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-13.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1973; F-233-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-14.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, 1974 - 1977; F-233-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-15.
  - Correspondence, 1974; F-233-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-16.
  - Correspondence, 1975; F-233-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-17.
  - Correspondence, 1975 - 1977; F-233-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-18.
  - Reports, 1974 - 1975; F-233-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-19.
  - Reports, 1975 - 1977; F-233-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-20.
  - Reports, 1976 - 1981; F-233-2-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-21.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1979; F-233-2-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 233-29)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-22.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1979; F-233-2-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-23.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-24.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-25.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-26.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-27.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 5, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-28.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 6, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-29.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 7, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-30.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 8, 1980; F-233-2-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-31.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-32.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-33.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 233-30)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-34.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-35.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 5, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-36.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 6, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-37.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 7, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-38.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 8, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-39.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 9, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-40.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 10, 1981; F-233-2-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-41.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1982; F-233-2-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-42.
  - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1982; F-233-2-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 233-31)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-3-0-43.
- Committee files, 1965 - 2000; F-233-3; 4.7 m of textual records 1 sound recording; Physical description: includes 4 audio cassettes (located in sub-series 3).
  Series consists of the records of committees of the Faculty of Education and documents their activities and deliberations. Records include meeting agendas, minutes, supporting papers, committee correspondence, and reports; also includes one sound recording relating to an Extraordinary Faculty Meeting in April 1978 (sub-series 3, file 30).
  The arrangement of this series into sub-series was provided by SFU Archives on the basis of the creating bodies. Each committee has been assigned its own sub-series. One artificial grouping (sub-series 1, "Commitee files - general") was created for files that deal with more than one commitee. The numbering of the sub-series (with the exception of sub-series 1) is based on chronology using the date range of the records as of July 2008. As future accruals are processed, however, the chronological order may get out of sync.
  Committee records of the pre-1972 centres and departments were generally integrated with the general office files for those units; see the various sub-series in series 4, "Centres and departments files".
  An alphabetical listing of all commitees has been included at the head of the file list to facilitate access.
  - Committees - general files, 1971 - 1995; F-233-3-1; 3 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to Faculty of Education committees in general. Records include a minute book containing draft minutes of the meetings of various committees (eventually written up as formal minutes); and the faculty's annual listing of its committees (functions, composition, terms of office, membership).
    - Mintue books (various committees), 1971 - 1976; F-233-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 233-32)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-5-0-5.
    - Committees of the Faculty of Education, 1976 - 1995; F-233-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 233-41)
  - Executive Committee files, 1965 - 2000; F-233-3-2; 1.83 m of textual records; Faculty of Education. Executive Committee
    A central committee charged with coordinating the activities and programs of the faculty has existed since the Faculty of Education began operations in 1965. It was originally called the Executive Council (1965-1967), then the Coordinating Council (1967-1972), before becoming the Executive Committee in 1972, under which name it continues to operate as of this writing (July 2008). In addition to its coordinating function, the committee reviews programs and activities and makes recommendations to the appropriate faculty bodies, and it prepares the agenda and documentation for the monthly Faculty Meeting. The composition of the committee has varied over time. Prior to 1972, members included the Dean, the Chairs of the Centres, and the Heads of Departments. After 1972 it comprised the Dean (and Associate Dean from 1983) and the Directors of the program areas.
    Sub-series consists of the agendas, minutes, and supporting papers of the meetings of the Executive Committee. Supporting papers include reports, proposals and recommendations, correspondence, policies, budget papers, capital budget requests, teaching / research schedules and office allocations, and course proposals and descriptions.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1965; F-233-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-1.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1967 - 1968; F-233-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-1.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1969; F-233-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-2.
    - Papers 01-14, 1969; F-233-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-3.
    - Papers 15-31, 1969; F-233-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-4.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1970; F-233-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-5.
    - Papers 29-47, 1970; F-233-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-6.
    - Papers 48-67, 1970; F-233-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-7.
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1971; F-233-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-6-0-8.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1973; F-233-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-2.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1974; F-233-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-3.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1975; F-233-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-4.
    - Papers EX 75, 01-23, 1975; F-233-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-8.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1976; F-233-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-5.
    - Papers EX 76, 01-28, 1976; F-233-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-9.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1977; F-233-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 233-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-6.
    - Papers EX 77, 01-14, 1977; F-233-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - small 233-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-10.
    - Papers EX 77, 15-23, 1977; F-233-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - small 233-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-11.
    - Papers EX 77, 24-38, 1977; F-233-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - small 233-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-12.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1978; F-233-3-2-0-20 (Archival box - small 233-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-7.
    - Papers EX 78, 01-18, 1978; F-233-3-2-0-21 (Archival box - small 233-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-13.
    - Papers EX 78, 19-33, 1978; F-233-3-2-0-22 (Archival box - small 233-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-3-2-0-14.
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1980; F-233-3-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 233-15)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1980; F-233-3-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 233-15)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1980; F-233-3-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 233-15)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1980; F-233-3-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 233-15)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1981; F-233-3-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 233-15)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1981; F-233-3-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 233-15)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1981; F-233-3-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 233-16)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1982; F-233-3-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 233-16)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1982; F-233-3-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 233-16)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1982; F-233-3-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 233-16)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1982; F-233-3-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 233-16)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1983; F-233-3-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 233-25)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1983; F-233-3-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 233-25)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1983; F-233-3-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 233-25)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1983; F-233-3-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 233-25)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1984; F-233-3-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 233-16)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1984; F-233-3-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 233-17)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1984; F-233-3-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 233-17)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1984; F-233-3-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 233-17)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 5, 1984; F-233-3-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 233-17)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1985; F-233-3-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 233-17)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1985; F-233-3-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 233-17)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1985; F-233-3-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 233-18)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1985; F-233-3-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 233-18)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 5, 1985; F-233-3-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 233-18)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1986; F-233-3-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 233-18)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1986; F-233-3-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 233-18)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1986; F-233-3-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 233-18)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 4, 1986; F-233-3-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 233-19)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 1, 1987; F-233-3-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 233-19)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 2, 1987; F-233-3-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 233-19)
    - Agenda, minutes, supporting papers, vol. 3, 1987; F-233-3-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 233-19)